import { IExercise } from "../types/IExercise";

export const exercises: IExercise[] = [
  {
    id: "ex-1",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Contains Duplicate",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/contains-duplicate/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/contains-duplicate",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-2",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Valid Anagram",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-anagram",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-3",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Two Sum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/two-sum",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-4",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Group Anagrams",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/group-anagrams/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/group-anagrams",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-5",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Top K Frequent Elements",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/top-k-frequent-elements/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/top-k-frequent-elements",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-6",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Encode and Decode Strings",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/encode-and-decode-strings/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/encode-and-decode-strings",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-7",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Product of Array Except Self",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/product-of-array-except-self/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/product-of-array-except-self",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-8",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Valid Sudoku",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-sudoku/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-sudoku",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-9",
    nodeId: "1",
    problem: "Longest Consecutive Sequence",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-consecutive-sequence/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-consecutive-sequence",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-10",
    nodeId: "2",
    problem: "Valid Palindrome",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-palindrome/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-palindrome",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-11",
    nodeId: "2",
    problem: "Two Sum II Input Array Is Sorted",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum-ii-input-array-is-sorted/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/two-sum-ii-input-array-is-sorted",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-12",
    nodeId: "2",
    problem: "3Sum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/3sum/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/3sum",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-13",
    nodeId: "2",
    problem: "Container With Most Water",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/container-with-most-water/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/container-with-most-water",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-14",
    nodeId: "2",
    problem: "Trapping Rain Water",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/trapping-rain-water/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/trapping-rain-water",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-15",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Valid Parentheses",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-parentheses",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-16",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Min Stack",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-stack/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/min-stack",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-17",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Evaluate Reverse Polish Notation",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/evaluate-reverse-polish-notation/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/evaluate-reverse-polish-notation",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-18",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Generate Parentheses",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/generate-parentheses/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/generate-parentheses",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-19",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Daily Temperatures",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/daily-temperatures/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/daily-temperatures",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-20",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Car Fleet",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/car-fleet/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/car-fleet",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-21",
    nodeId: "3",
    problem: "Largest Rectangle In Histogram",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-rectangle-in-histogram/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/largest-rectangle-in-histogram",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-22",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Binary Search",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-search/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-search",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-23",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Search a 2D Matrix",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-a-2d-matrix/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/search-a-2d-matrix",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-24",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Koko Eating Bananas",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/koko-eating-bananas/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/koko-eating-bananas",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-25",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Find Minimum In Rotated Sorted Array",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-minimum-in-rotated-sorted-array/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-minimum-in-rotated-sorted-array",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-26",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Search In Rotated Sorted Array",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/search-in-rotated-sorted-array",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-27",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Time Based Key Value Store",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/time-based-key-value-store/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/time-based-key-value-store",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-28",
    nodeId: "4",
    problem: "Median of Two Sorted Arrays",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/median-of-two-sorted-arrays/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/median-of-two-sorted-arrays",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-29",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Best Time to Buy And Sell Stock",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-30",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Longest Substring Without Repeating Characters",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-31",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Longest Repeating Character Replacement",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-repeating-character-replacement/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-repeating-character-replacement",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-32",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Permutation in String",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutation-in-string/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/permutation-in-string",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-33",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Minimum Window Substring",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-window-substring/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/minimum-window-substring",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-34",
    nodeId: "5",
    problem: "Sliding Window Maximum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sliding-window-maximum/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/sliding-window-maximum",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-35",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Reverse Linked List",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-linked-list",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-36",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Merge Two Sorted Lists",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-two-sorted-lists/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-two-sorted-lists",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-37",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Reorder List",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reorder-list/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/reorder-list",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-38",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Remove Nth Node From End of List",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-39",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Copy List With Random Pointer",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/copy-list-with-random-pointer/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/copy-list-with-random-pointer",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-40",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Add Two Numbers",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/add-two-numbers/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/add-two-numbers",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-41",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Linked List Cycle",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/linked-list-cycle",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-42",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Find The Duplicate Number",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-duplicate-number/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-the-duplicate-number",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-43",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "LRU Cache",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lru-cache/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/lru-cache",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-44",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Merge K Sorted Lists",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-k-sorted-lists/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-k-sorted-lists",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-45",
    nodeId: "6",
    problem: "Reverse Nodes In K Group",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-nodes-in-k-group/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-nodes-in-k-group",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-46",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Invert Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/invert-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/invert-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-47",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Maximum Depth of Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-48",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Diameter of Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/diameter-of-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/diameter-of-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-49",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Balanced Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/balanced-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/balanced-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-50",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Same Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/same-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-51",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Subtree of Another Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subtree-of-another-tree/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/subtree-of-another-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-52",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Search Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-53",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Binary Tree Level Order Traversal",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-level-order-traversal",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-54",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Binary Tree Right Side View",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-right-side-view/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-right-side-view",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-55",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Count Good Nodes In Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-56",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Validate Binary Search Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/validate-binary-search-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-57",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Kth Smallest Element In a Bst",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-58",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Construct Binary Tree From Preorder And Inorder Traversal",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-59",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Binary Tree Maximum Path Sum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-60",
    nodeId: "7",
    problem: "Serialize And Deserialize Binary Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-61",
    nodeId: "8",
    problem: "Implement Trie Prefix Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-trie-prefix-tree/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/implement-trie-prefix-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-62",
    nodeId: "8",
    problem: "Design Add And Search Words Data Structure",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-add-and-search-words-data-structure/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/design-add-and-search-words-data-structure",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-63",
    nodeId: "8",
    problem: "Word Search II",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search-ii/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-search-ii",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-64",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Subsets",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/subsets",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-65",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Combination Sum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/combination-sum",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-66",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Permutations",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/permutations",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-67",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Subsets II",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets-ii/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/subsets-ii",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-68",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Combination Sum II",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-ii/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/combination-sum-ii",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-69",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Word Search",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-search",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-70",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Palindrome Partitioning",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-partitioning/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/palindrome-partitioning",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-71",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "Letter Combinations of a Phone Number",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-72",
    nodeId: "9",
    problem: "N Queens",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/n-queens/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/n-queens",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-73",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Kth Largest Element In a Stream",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-74",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Last Stone Weight",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/last-stone-weight/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/last-stone-weight",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-75",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "K Closest Points to Origin",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/k-closest-points-to-origin/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/k-closest-points-to-origin",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-76",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Kth Largest Element In An Array",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-largest-element-in-an-array",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-77",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Task Scheduler",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/task-scheduler/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/task-scheduler",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-78",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Design Twitter",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-twitter/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/design-twitter",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-79",
    nodeId: "10",
    problem: "Find Median From Data Stream",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-median-from-data-stream",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-80",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Number of Islands",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-islands/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/number-of-islands",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-81",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Max Area of Island",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-area-of-island/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/max-area-of-island",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-82",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Clone Graph",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/clone-graph/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/clone-graph",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-83",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Walls And Gates",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/walls-and-gates/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/walls-and-gates",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-84",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Rotting Oranges",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotting-oranges/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/rotting-oranges",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-85",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Pacific Atlantic Water Flow",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pacific-atlantic-water-flow/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/pacific-atlantic-water-flow",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-86",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Surrounded Regions",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/surrounded-regions/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/surrounded-regions",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-87",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Course Schedule",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/course-schedule",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-88",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Course Schedule II",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule-ii/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/course-schedule-ii",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-89",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Graph Valid Tree",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/graph-valid-tree/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/graph-valid-tree",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-90",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Number of Connected Components In An Undirected Graph",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-connected-components-in-an-undirected-graph/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution:
      "https://neetcode.io/solutions/number-of-connected-components-in-an-undirected-graph",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-91",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Redundant Connection",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/redundant-connection/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/redundant-connection",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-92",
    nodeId: "11",
    problem: "Word Ladder",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-ladder/",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-ladder",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-93",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Climbing Stairs",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/climbing-stairs/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/climbing-stairs",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-94",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Min Cost Climbing Stairs",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-cost-climbing-stairs/",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/min-cost-climbing-stairs",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-95",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "House Robber",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/house-robber",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-96",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "House Robber II",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber-ii/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/house-robber-ii",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-97",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Longest Palindromic Substring",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-palindromic-substring",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-98",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Palindromic Substrings",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindromic-substrings/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/palindromic-substrings",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-99",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Decode Ways",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/decode-ways/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/decode-ways",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-100",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Coin Change",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/coin-change",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-101",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Maximum Product Subarray",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-subarray/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/maximum-product-subarray",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-102",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Word Break",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-break/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-break",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-103",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-increasing-subsequence",
  },
  {
    id: "ex-104",
    nodeId: "12",
    problem: "Partition Equal Subset Sum",
    link: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-equal-subset-sum/",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    solution: "https://neetcode.io/solutions/partition-equal-subset-sum",
  },
];
